http://www.cdcnpin.org/pages/policies-and-disclaimers#privacy

Skip to main content
To Join the NPIN community Sign In or Sign up
Home
HIV/AIDS
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention ResourcesTrainingBasicsGuidelines and RecommendationsSurveillance and Statistics
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention ResourcesTrainingBasicsGuidelines and RecommendationsSurveillance and Statistics
Introducing NPIN’s Social Community
Want to improve your HIV program? Don’t reinvent the wheel another HIV prevention professional already created. Join NPIN’s new social community to connect, share, and collaborate.
Viral Hepatitis
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention Program PracticesTrainingBasicsSurveillance and StatisticsGuidelines and Recommendations
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention Program PracticesTrainingBasicsSurveillance and StatisticsGuidelines and Recommendations
Introducing NPIN’s Social Community
Where to go for the ABCs of viral hepatitis prevention? Join other professionals on NPIN’s new social community to connect, share, and collaborate.
STDs
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention ResourcesTrainingBasicsSurveillance and StatisticsGuidelines and Recommendations
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention ResourcesTrainingBasicsSurveillance and StatisticsGuidelines and Recommendations
Introducing NPIN’s Social Community
Talk sexual health services with other STD prevention professionals. Join NPIN’s new social community to connect, share, and collaborate.
Tuberculosis
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention ResourcesTrainingBasicsSurveillance and StatisticsGuidelines and Recommendationsfindtbresources.cdc.gov
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention ResourcesTrainingBasicsSurveillance and StatisticsGuidelines and Recommendationsfindtbresources.cdc.gov
Introducing NPIN’s Social Community
Looking for a place to discuss TB best practices, resources, and challenges? Connect, share, and collaborate with other prevention professionals.
School Health
Training
Surveillance and Statistics Resources
Prevention Resources
Digital Media
Best Practices and Resources
Basics
Training
HIV/AIDSViral HepatitisSTDTuberculosisSchool HealthSocial Media Health Literacy
Health Communication
Health Communication StrategiesCampaign ResourcesAnnual ObservancesCultural Competence
NPIN Community
NPIN Community Group Preview
Home » Policies and Procedures For The National Prevention Information Network
COVID-19 Information |
En Español
For COVID-19 testing information please visit: https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/symptoms-testing/testing.html
Directly contact organizations to find out about changes to services or hours.
Service FinderMaterialsFundingCampaignsCommunityDigital Media ToolsPrevention ResourcesTrainingBasicsGuidelines and RecommendationsSurveillance and Statistics
Recommend on Facebook
Follow on Twitter
HIV Content Notice
Community Terms of Use
Organizations Database Inclusion Policy
Organizations Database Information Request Policy
About Links to Other Sites
Privacy Policy
HIV Content Notice
This site contains HIV prevention messages that may not be appropriate for all audiences. Since HIV infection is spread primarily through sexual practices or by sharing needles, prevention messages and programs may address these topics. If you are not seeking such information or may be offended by such materials, please exit this Website.
Community Terms of Use
These Terms of Use apply to your use of the National Prevention Information Network (NPIN) community. You are solely responsible for your conduct and your content in the community and compliance with these terms. By registering with us or using or browsing this community, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these terms. This community is not directed to anyone younger than 13 and is offered only to users 13 years of age or older. Any person who provides their personal information through this community represents that they are 13 years of age or older.
Organizations Database Inclusion Policy
To be included in the NPIN Organizations Database, organizations must focus their services on one or more of the disease areas of NPIN (HIV/AIDS, viral hepatitis, STDs, or TB) or offer specific programs targeting one or more of these diseases. View the full policy for more information on which types of organizations and services are included.
If you have questions about NPIN's Organizations Database policy, please contact us at NPIN-Info@cdc.gov.
Organizations Database Information Request Policy
NPIN's organizations database information request policy outlines the process for submitting requests for NPIN organizations data. If you have questions, please contact us at NPIN-Info@cdc.gov.
User Privacy
Your mobile number will not be shared or used for any other purpose.
User Fees
The service does not charge recipients to receive text messages. Message and data rates may apply.
Privacy Policy
NPIN Privacy Policy
Help
If you have questions or problems, or need assistance, please Contact the National Prevention Information Network (NPIN).
About Links to Other Sites
The CDC and NPIN are not responsible for the availability or content of external sites, nor do we endorse, warrant, or guarantee the services or information described or offered on the sites. Further, the sites you visit may contain information that may not be appropriate for all audiences. The views and information provided on these external Websites do not necessarily state or reflect those of the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, CDC, or NPIN.
If you have any difficulties or concerns with any linked sites, please e-mail us.
Privacy Policy
The CDC National Prevention Information Network (NPIN) respects the privacy of visitors to the NPIN Website and community. The community is a peer-to-peer online collaborative platform designed and developed by NPIN to address the critical and ongoing needs of CDC partners. NPIN does not provide personal identifying information to any outside organization or any government agency.
Privacy Statement
Why is information collected?
What information is collected?
What information is not collected?
What about Site Security?
Can I opt-out?
Questions
Privacy Act Statement
If you choose to provide us with business information – by registering on the site, managing your profile or filling out a Contact Us form with your work e-mail and/or work postal addresses and any other information – we use that information to improve usability or respond to your message. If you register for an eNgage account, NPIN might use that information in the future to reach out to you about NPIN products, services and offerings. For your protection, we recommend you not provide any non-work related information. With your information, we cross reference data to perform statistical analysis to better discern the characteristics of those interested in site content or eNgage content so that we can improve the user experience. We will only share information with another government agency if your inquiry relates to that agency, or as otherwise required by law. We never give individual profiles or give information to any private organization.
CDCNPIN never collects information for commercial marketing and is not a system of record. While you must provide an e-mail address or postal address for a response other than those generated automatically in response to questions or comments that you may submit, we recommend that you NOT include any other personal information, especially Social Security numbers. The Social Security Administration offers additional guidance on sharing your Social Security number.
Why is information collected?
We may collect a limited amount of information on usage of the Website and community for statistical purposes to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our site and members of the eNgage community with the goal of helping us make our site more useful to visitors and the community.
What information is collected?
The information collected includes standard server log information, such as the domain name or IP address from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site; the pages you viewed; the type of browser and operating system you used to access our site; and, if you linked to our site from another Website, that Website's address. We collect this information on an aggregate basis only. Our Website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. For example, we track which pages are most popular among visitors as a whole, but pages viewed are not identified with individual users.
For site management, information is collected for statistical purposes. This NPIN system uses software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.  Participation in the community is personally identified to you but only if you choose to provide such information to us to join and participate.
When inquiries are sent to us via e-mail, we store the question and the e-mail address information so that we can respond electronically.
What information is not collected?
Unless otherwise required by statute, we do not identify publicly who sends questions or comments to our Website or community. We will not obtain information that will allow us to personally identify you when you visit our Website, unless you choose to provide such information to us to participate in the community.
What about Site Security?
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this NPIN computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are scheduled for regular destruction in accordance with National Archives and Records Administration guidelines.
Can I opt-Out?
At any time, you may choose to opt out of the community. When you do this, your request is immediately honored.
Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.
Questions
If you have additional questions or comments about the Website and community or about the information presented here, please send them to us at e-mail us.
Copyright Status Disclaimer
CDC and other government information included on the NPIN Website is in the public domain; however, you will encounter information that is owned/created by others, including copyrighted materials and other materials sponsored by private companies or non-government organizations. Those other parties retain all rights to publish or reproduce those documents or to allow others to do so. Any copyrighted materials included on this site remain the property of their respective owners/creators and should not be reproduced or otherwise used. It is not the intent of NPIN to violate or infringe upon any copyrights. If you believe we have done so, please e-mail us, and we will take care of the matter promptly.
Liability Disclaimer
NPIN does not warrant or assume any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, apparatus, product, or process disclosed in abstracts or documents available from the NPIN Website.
Medical Information Disclaimer
NPIN does not intend to provide specific medical advice, but we may provide Website visitors with information to better understand their health and risk factors for specific diseases. NPIN urges you to consult with a qualified health care provider for diagnosis and answers to your personal health questions.
Technical Requirements
If you have any difficulties or concerns with the site's display or functionality, please visit our Help page or e-mail us, and be sure to include the name and version of the browser you're using.
Photo Disclaimer
The people in the photographs that appear on this Web site are models and used for illustrative purposes only.
Password Policy
The NPIN Website password policy has been established according to CDC IT security requirements. The purpose of this policy is to protect community members' personal information, as well as the integrity and availability of the site against potential intrusion and unauthorized access. As such, community members are responsible for taking the appropriate steps, as outlined below, to create and maintain their passwords.
Passwords must meet the following requirements:
Must be updated every 60 days.
Must contain at least 8 characters.
Must contain three out of the four following four types of characters:
Lowercase
Uppercase
Numbers
Special characters (! #$%^&*(){}[])
Must be different than the previous 6 passwords.
Must not contain the user ID or any part of user’s full name.
Must be 75% different than the current password.
